perfume.com 2010-12-02

# Security And Privacy Policy : Shop Perfume.com

## Security And Privacy Policy Back

**Is your website secure?**

At Perfume.com, we promise that your personal information is secure. Every transaction is processed by the Bank of America using the latest industry standards for secure online credit card transactions. Secure servers protect your information using advanced encryption and firewall technology throughout the ordering process. Please never send your credit card information via email.

Once your transaction is complete we DO NOT store your credit card number anywhere, further protecting you.

We use 128bit encryption through SSL servers using GEOTrust Secure Certificates. Our servers are state of the art Dell machines running the most recent versions Linux Operating Systems and Software. All security patches are updated regularily. We take internet security VERY seriously and make every effort possible to insure your credit card information and identity are protected.

If you have any concerns with sending sensitive information over the internet, please call our customer service line at 1-800-645-9251 and we will gladly take your order over the telephone.

**What is your privacy policy?**

Perfume.com is committed to our visitors and to protecting their privacy. We value our visitors and endeavor to create an enjoyable and valuable experience when visiting our network of sites. The following Privacy Policy applies to all visitors to the Perfume.com network of sites, and to all referrals made by our visitors.

**What information do we collect?**

When you place an order from our web site, we may collect the following information in order to promptly and securely process your order: your name, telephone number, email address, billing information (credit card number, expiration date and billing address), products purchased and promotional codes.

**How do we use customer information?**

We use information we collect from you to process your orders and to email you special promotional offers and discounts from Perfume.com. We never share your personal information with any third party.

**Customer Protection**

Perfume.com takes all measures to provide a safe environment with security procedures in place to ensure proper storage and careful retrieval of information so that nothing improper happens to your personal information while under our control.

**Fraud Protection**

All payment forms are subject to verification and review by Perufme.com. Perfume.com reserves the right to refuse to process any transaction, sale, or shipment of orders due to suspected fraud or unauthorized or illegal activity.

**What we do with your information?**

Your privacy is a very sensitive subject for us and we take it very seriously. So our privacy policy is simple: we will not sell, barter, give away or rent your personal information to any third party outside of Perfume.com, Inc. and its properties. Perfume.com may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third parties, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

**What are cookies?**

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computers hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. We may use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, record user specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to the site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads and customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

**Your consent**

By using our Web site and submitting your information to the Perfume.com network, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Perfume.com, Inc. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If you are not comfortable with any of the changes to our Privacy Policy, you will have the opportunity of un-submitting your information from our network at any time.

**Links**

Some sites within our network contain links to other sites. Perfume.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. If you have a question about the privacy policy of those web sites, please visit them directly.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, our site practices, or your personal experience dealing with this web site, you can [Contact](http://www.perfume.com/contact_us) our office.

## Back
